We also have grammar checker, so this would be cool as well.
Let's see if we can get any kind of grammatic errors from a purely AI generator text by
actually.
So as you see over here, we have a non title document and again, we can upload a document
or either upload a document or paste our text over here.
So I right click and click paste and I'm looking for my grammatic errors, right?
What are my errors but chat GPD errors by the Quillbot AI?
So I wait.
Right?
We have 18 grammatic suggestions, so it has removed the space at a period, at a period.
These are all about the French phrases, it's a little bit weird because you know, but
whatever, yep, these are the grammatic errors, right?
So this is also the grammar checker which can be very, very helpful again when it comes
to writing and we can also specify a very specific writing task.
So it can optimize the grammar for that very purpose, either it is a research paper, business
email, marketing copy, essay, you know, academic article or anything like that.
So we can enter a writing task and we can get better results specifying and personalizing
it that way.